<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Good Wobbles</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Good Wobbles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 17:51:49 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime Lab New York Intership: Post-Mortem</title>
      <link>/2019/09/crime-lab-new-york-intership-post-mortem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 17:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/09/crime-lab-new-york-intership-post-mortem/</guid>
      <description>I spent this past summer in New York City, interning for an amazing organization: Crime Lab New York, a member of the University of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Urban Labs system. I got to spend a lot of time learning about a lot of things that I had, frankly, never even thought to think about!
Given just how much I&amp;rsquo;ve learned this summer, I thought it might be beneficial to myself (and whomever might come across this blog/portfolio) to do a post-mortem of my time at CLNY.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Quick D&amp;D Experiment</title>
      <link>/1/01/a-quick-dd-experiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1/01/a-quick-dd-experiment/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick experiment I was curious about! A few friends and I are starting up a new D&amp;amp;D campaign, and a player asked me how I prefer stats for characters to be determined. I&amp;rsquo;ve always preferred point buying, but I enjoy the randomness of rolling stats. I ran some simulations to get an idea of what kind of stat distributions different rolling methods give!
First, we define our functions for generating stats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Analysis of the Competitive Lifetime of Powerlifters</title>
      <link>/1/01/an-analysis-of-the-competitive-lifetime-of-powerlifters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1/01/an-analysis-of-the-competitive-lifetime-of-powerlifters/</guid>
      <description>Brief overview
A survival analysis is conducted on the OpenPowerlifting.org dataset. Individual powerlifters and the length of time that they&amp;rsquo;ve been active (in terms of time from first to last meet and number of meets attended) are treated as survival objects. Survival curves are fitted and covariates are examined for effects.
This project was completed in part as a semester project for a Reliability Data Analysis course at the University of South Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>The easiest way to contact me is by email, which I usually check a couple of times a day at minimum.
Email: sean.ch.carter@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating Random Graphs</title>
      <link>/1/01/generating-random-graphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1/01/generating-random-graphs/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post is still undergoing &amp;lsquo;renovation&amp;rsquo; - images need to be cleaned up and mathematical notation inserted, but the core content is readable and correct.
Graphs are among the most basic and widely applicable mathematical structures. Modern applications in the study of social networks, spread of communicable diseases, computer networks, and many others, have made the study of graphs and their probabilistic counterpart, random graphs, especially relevant.
As a way of learning more about networks, I investigated algorithms for generating random graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Walkers and Web Crawlers</title>
      <link>/1/01/random-walkers-and-web-crawlers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1/01/random-walkers-and-web-crawlers/</guid>
      <description>Brief Overview: This was put together for a class assignment in Probability Theory 2. We were to discuss random walks and how they relate to the PageRank algorithm.
An overview of the relevant mathematics is given, and a small web crawler is implemented to collect links between wikipedia articles. The links are saved in a SQLite database and used later to construct a graph and rank articles based on centrality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whose Wobbles Are Wholesome And Good</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! You&amp;rsquo;ve found the blog/portfolio of Sean Carter! I&amp;rsquo;m a graduate student in Statistics at the University of South Florida.
Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve found that many projects that I work on eventually get &amp;ldquo;lost to the void&amp;rdquo;. I wanted to have a place where I could put any interesting work that I do so I can refer back to it later and share it with other people. This is basically the home of all of my projects going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>