<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Good Wobbles</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Good Wobbles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Analysis of the Competitive Lifetime of Powerlifters</title>
      <link>https://example.com/1/01/an-analysis-of-the-competitive-lifetime-of-powerlifters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/1/01/an-analysis-of-the-competitive-lifetime-of-powerlifters/</guid>
      <description>Brief overview
A survival analysis is conducted on the OpenPowerlifting.org dataset. Individual powerlifters and the length of time that they&amp;rsquo;ve been active (in terms of time from first to last meet and number of meets attended) are treated as survival objects. Survival curves are fitted and covariates are examined for effects.
This project was completed in part as a semester project for a Reliability Data Analysis course at the University of South Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: sean.ch.carter@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating Random Graphs</title>
      <link>https://example.com/1/01/generating-random-graphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/1/01/generating-random-graphs/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post is still undergoing &amp;lsquo;renovation&amp;rsquo; - images need to be cleaned up and mathematical notation inserted, but the core content is readable and correct.
Graphs are among the most basic and widely applicable mathematical structures. Modern applications in the study of social networks, spread of communicable diseases, computer networks, and many others, have made the study of graphs and their probabilistic counterpart, random graphs, especially relevant.
As a way of learning more about networks, I investigated algorithms for generating random graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whose Wobbles Are Wholesome And Good</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! You&amp;rsquo;ve found the blog/portfolio of Sean Carter! I&amp;rsquo;m a graduate student in Statistics at the University of South Florida.
This is basically the home of all of my projects going forward. Anything I share here, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to point out difficulties I ran into and solutions I came up with, so that hopefully you won&amp;rsquo;t have to do the same amount of googling that I did!
My blog title comes from a topic I studied as an undergraduate in Molecular Biology: Wobble Base Pairing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>